<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">BlackHole Cam</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="phototake_name">Photo</string>


    <string name="en_title_tab0_phenomenon">Description</string>
    <string name="en_title_tab1_phenomenon">Support</string>
    <string name="en_progress_title">Saving image</string>
    <string name="en_progress_msg">Wait while processing</string>
    <string name="en_could_not_save_img1">Image could not be saved</string>
    <string name="en_could_not_open_folder">Cannot open/create the image folder</string>
    <string name="en_saved_img1">Image saved</string>
    <string name="en_saving_img_to_sd">Saving processed image to the card</string>
    <string name="en_choose_mass">Select black hole mass</string>
    <string name="en_mass_unit_suffix">of the Earth mass</string>
    <string name="en_menu_openfolder">Open image folder</string>
    <string name="en_menu_preferences">Description</string>
    <string name="en_menu_aboutapp">Support</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon1">
       This application demonstrates the gravitational effect of an small black hole nearby you.
       It uses a back camera of your mobile phone, to see the environment, and then it deflects the
       light rays according to the black hole gravitational pull. The whole effect is called the
       gravitational lens, and can be understood by looking at the picture(1) below - black hole as an red object in the center:
    </string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon1_linkify">gravitational lens</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon1_link">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gravitational_lens</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon2">
        You can change the black hole mass by touching the screen with two fingers and then pinching or spreading them.
        Or, you can use the bottom-right black button to do the same - as you can see then, the black hole mass is of the
        order of inner planet mass - like mars or almost the earth. By clicking the big camera button in the middle,
        you can save the full-resolution image with the black hole on your phone storage card into the separate MyBlackHoles folder
        (use the menu option in the app to find the folder easier).
        The gravity lens here tries to be as accurate, as possible - yet it still assumes that all that the camera sees is very far away -
        which does not have to be necessarily true - especially for the object close to you. Also, the approximation is not very accurate close to the event horizon (black circle
        in the middle - corresponding to the real size of the event horizon) - because the phone camera has only some narrow, limited
        field of view - so the artifacts close to the event horizon are unavoidable here. Black hole in this app is assumed to be always 1 meter (3.28ft) away from you - the effect of increasing this distance would have
        exactly the same effect as decreasing black hole mass. Non-rotating black hole is being used - something known as the
        Schwarzschild solution of the field equations for spherically-symetrical object.
        \n
        Field of view of your back camera, as reported by the phone:\n\n
        horizontal: XXXXXX degrees\n
        vertical  : YYYYYY degrees.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Credit for the Andrew Hamilton for the picture.
    </string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon2_linkify">Schwarzschild solution</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon2_link">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schwarzschild_metric</string>
    <string name="en_about_app_description1">
        Thank you for using this app, please rate it, whether you like it or not :)
        It is completely free and without advertisements. Paid version on the store is only for donation purposes.\n\n
        If you would like to support me in further progress, bugfixing, translation improvement,
        you can always donate any amount you like :)\n\n
        Or you can visit my small webpage for this app.\n
        \n
        Requires android 4.2 or more, + support for 32-bit floats on GPU to correctly simulate black hole on the camera preview(OpenGL).
        Final, high-resolution image saved on memory card is rendered on CPU in a multi-threaded fashion (depending on the number
        of physical cores on the phone).
    </string>

    <string name="en_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_en.html</string>
    <string name="en_ovh_page1_linkify">webpage</string>
    <string name="en_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="en_donation_link1_linkify">donate</string>



    <string name="pl_title_tab0_phenomenon">Opis</string>
    <string name="pl_title_tab1_phenomenon">Wsparcie</string>
    <string name="pl_progress_title">Zapisywanie obrazu</string>
    <string name="pl_progress_msg">Czekaj, przetwarzam</string>
    <string name="pl_could_not_save_img1">Nie udało się zapisać obrazu</string>
    <string name="pl_saved_img1">Obraz zapisano</string>
    <string name="pl_saving_img_to_sd">Zapisywanie przetworzonego obrazka na kartę</string>
    <string name="pl_could_not_open_folder">Nie mogę otworzyć folderu z obrazkami</string>
    <string name="pl_choose_mass">Wybierz masę czarnej dziury</string>
    <string name="pl_mass_unit_suffix">masy Ziemii</string>
    <string name="pl_menu_openfolder">Otwórz folder obrazków</string>
    <string name="pl_menu_preferences">Opis</string>
    <string name="pl_menu_aboutapp">Wsparcie</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon1">
       Ta aplikacja obrazuje efekt grawitacji czarnej dziury na otoczenie. Używa ona tylnej kamerki telefonu
        do rejestracji obrazu i ugięcia promieni świetlnych zgodnie z masą i odległością czarnej dziury od obserwatora.
        Cały efekt nosi nazwę soczewki grawitacyjnej, i jest zobrazowany na obrazku(1) poniżej - czarna dziura jako czerwony obiek w centrum:

    </string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon1_linkify">soczewki grawitacyjnej</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon1_link">https://pl.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soczewkowanie_grawitacyjne</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon2">
       Możesz zmieniać masę czarnej dziury poprzez gest przybliżenia i oddalenia dwoma palcami na ekranie aplikacji. Albo, ten sam
        efekt, wraz z informacją o masie, możesz uzyskać kilkając ikonę w dolnym prawym rogu. Jak widzisz,
        masa czarnej dziury możliwa do ustawienia jest rzędu wielkości mas takich planet jak Mars czy Ziemia.
        Klikając wielki przycisk kamerki na środku, możesz zapisać obrazek z czarną dziurą w pełnej rozdzielczości na kartę pamięci
        twojego telefonu do osobnego folderu MyBlackHoles (w menu opcji jest pozycja co przeniesie cię do tego folderu automatycznie).
        Efekt soczewki grawitacyjnej tutaj stara się być tak wierny rzeczywistości jak możliwe - ale ciągle poddany jest pewnym założeniom uproszczającym -
        jak to że obraz widziany przez kamerkę jest znacznie dalej od czarnej dziury - co nie musi być prawdą dla przedmiotów obok ciebie (kamerka telefonu nie wie jak daleko są widziane przez nią obiekty).
        Również przybliżenie bardzo blisko horyzontu zdarzeń
        (czarne kółko na środku - odpowiadające rzeczywistemu rozmiarowi kątowemu horyzontu zdarzeń)
        nie jest dobre i generuje pewne nieścisłości - kamerka telefonu ma pewne ograniczenie kątowe pola widzenia i promienie światła przechodzące
        zbyt blisko horyzontu zdarzeń nie mają szansy trafić do obserwatora z obszaru widzenia kamerki, gdyż byłyby uginane zbyt mocno.\n
        Czarna dziura jest umiejscowiona w odległości 1m od kamery - zwiększenie tego dystansu 2x wpłynęłoby na obraz tak samo jak zmniejszenie masy
        czarnej dziury dwukrotnie.
        Przybliżone rozwiązanie Schwarzchilda równań ogólnej teorii względności - statyczna, nierotująca czarna dziura, jest tutaj użyte do symulacji.\n
        Pole widzenia twojej tylnej kamery telefonu, wg. systemu:\n\n
        poziomo: XXXXXX stopni\n
        pionowo  : YYYYYY stopni.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Podziękowania za obrazek dla: Andrew Hamilton.
    </string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon2_linkify">rozwiązanie Schwarzchilda</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon2_link">https://pl.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metryka_Schwarzschilda</string>
    <string name="pl_about_app_description1">
        Dziękuję za skorzystanie z tej applikacji. Jest ona całkowicie darmowa i bez reklam - płatna
        jej wersja na Google Play store
        ma identyczną funkcjonalność i jest jedynie sposobem na wsparcie finansowe.\n\n
        Jeśli chciałbyś mnie wspomóc w dalszym rozwijaniu tej aplikacji, usuwaniu błędów,
        poprawy tłumaczenia, możesz zawsze udzielić wsparcia finansowego :) \n\n
        Możesz również odwiedzić moją małą stronę dla tej aplikacji.\n
        \n
        Wymaga androida 4.2 lub więcej, + wsparcie dla 32-bitowych liczb zmiennoprzecinkowych na GPU do prawidłowego symulowania podglądu(OpenGL). Finalny obraz
        o wysokiej rozdzielczości jest renderowany wielowątkowo na CPU (zależnie od ilości fizycznych rdzeni w telefonie).
    </string>
    <string name="pl_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_pl.html</string>
    <string name="pl_ovh_page1_linkify">stronę</string>
    <string name="pl_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="pl_donation_link1_linkify">wsparcia finansowego</string>















    <string name="zh_title_tab0_phenomenon">描述</string>
    <string name="zh_title_tab1_phenomenon">支持</string>
    <string name="zh_progress_title">保存图像</string>
    <string name="zh_progress_msg">等待处理</string>
    <string name="zh_could_not_save_img1">图像无法保存</string>
    <string name="zh_could_not_open_folder">无法打开/创建图像文件夹</string>
    <string name="zh_saved_img1">图像保存</string>
    <string name="zh_saving_img_to_sd">保存处理后的图像到存储卡</string>
    <string name="zh_choose_mass">选择黑洞质量</string>
    <string name="zh_mass_unit_suffix">地球质量</string>
    <string name="zh_menu_openfolder">打开图像文件夹</string>
    <string name="zh_menu_preferences">描述</string>
    <string name="zh_menu_aboutapp">支持</string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon1">
该应用程序演示附近你一个小的黑洞的引力效应。
       它使用移动电话的后照相机，看环境，然后将其偏转
       根据黑洞引力的光线。整个效果被称为
       引力透镜，并且可以通过查看下面的图片（1）可以理解 - 黑洞作为中心的红色物体：
    </string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon1_linkify">引力透镜</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="zh_description_phenomenon1_link">https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%BC%95%E5%8A%9B%E9%80%8F%E9%95%9C</string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon2">
     你可以用两个手指触摸屏幕，然后挤压或传播这些改变黑洞质量。
        或者，你可以使用右下角黑色按钮做同样的 - 你可以看到那么，黑洞质量的
        内行星质量的秩序 - 像火星或接近地球。点击中间的大拍照键，
        你可以用你的手机存储卡上的黑洞保存全分辨率图像分割成单独的文件夹MyBlackHoles
        （使用菜单选项中的应用程序，找到文件夹更容易）。
        这里的重力透镜努力做到准确，尽可能 - 但它仍然假定所有的摄像头看到很远的地方 -
        这并不必须是一定真 - 特别是对靠近你的对象。此外，近似不是很准确接近事件视界（黑圈
        在中间 - 对应于视界的实际大小） - 因为手机照相机仅具有一些窄，有限
        视野 - 如此接近的事件视界的文物是不可避免的在这里。在此应用程序黑洞被认为是始终为1米（3.28英尺）离你而去 - 增加这个距离才能产生的效果
        正是因为减小黑洞质量相同的效果。非旋转的黑洞正在使用 - 这被称为
        为球状对称物体的场方程的史瓦西解。
        \n
        看你的背部摄像头领域，所报告的电话：\n \n
        水平：XXXXXX 度的\n
        垂直：YYYYYY 度。
        \n
        \n
        （1）信用为安德鲁·汉密尔顿的图片。
    </string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon2_linkify">史瓦西解</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="zh_description_phenomenon2_link">https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%8F%B2%E7%93%A6%E8%A5%BF%E5%BA%A6%E8%A6%8F</string>
    <string name="zh_about_app_description1">
      感谢您使用这个程序，请评价它，不管你喜欢还是不喜欢 :)
        它是完全地免费，无广告。在商店付费版本仅用于捐赠目的。\n\n
        如果你想支持我的进一步进展，错误修复，提高翻译，
        你总是可以捐赠，你喜欢的任何金额 :)\n\n
        或者您也可以访问我为这个应用程序的小网页。\n
        \n
        需要Android4.2以上，+32位支持GPU上的浮正确模拟相机预览（OpenGL的）黑洞。
        保存在存储卡最后，高分辨率图像以多线程方式CPU上呈现（根据数
        在手机上物理核心）。
    </string>

    <string name="zh_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_zh.html</string>
    <string name="zh_ovh_page1_linkify">网页</string>
    <string name="zh_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="zh_donation_link1_linkify">捐赠</string>













    <string name="ja_title_tab0_phenomenon">説明</string>
    <string name="ja_title_tab1_phenomenon">サポート</string>
    <string name="ja_progress_title">画像保存</string>
    <string name="ja_progress_msg">処理中に待ち</string>
    <string name="ja_could_not_save_img1">画像は保存できませんでした</string>
    <string name="ja_could_not_open_folder">開いていない/画像フォルダを作成することができます</string>
    <string name="ja_saved_img1">画像保存</string>
    <string name="ja_saving_img_to_sd">カードに処理された画像を保存します</string>
    <string name="ja_choose_mass">ブラックホールの質量を選択</string>
    <string name="ja_mass_unit_suffix">地球の質量の</string>
    <string name="ja_menu_openfolder">オープン画像フォルダ</string>
    <string name="ja_menu_preferences">説明</string>
    <string name="ja_menu_aboutapp">サポート</string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon1">
       このアプリケーションは、あなたの近くの小さなブラックホールの重力の影響を示しています。
       これは、環境を確認するために、携帯電話のバックカメラを使用し、それは偏向します
       ブラックホール重力に従って光線。全体の効果が呼び出されます
       重力レンズは、以下の画像（1）を見ることによって理解することができる - 中央に赤いオブジェクトとしてブラックホール：
    </string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon1_linkify">重力レンズ</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ja_description_phenomenon1_link">https://ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E9%87%8D%E5%8A%9B%E3%83%AC%E3%83%B3%E3%82%BA</string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon2">
        あなたは、2本の指で画面をタッチし、それらをつまんまたは拡散によってブラックホールの質量を変更することができます。
        それとも、あなたが同じことを行うには、右下の黒いボタンを使用することができます - あなたが見ることができるように、ブラックホールの質量があります
        内側の惑星の質量の順 - 火星またはほぼ地球のような。中央に大きなカメラボタンをクリックすることにより、
        あなたは独立したMyBlackHolesフォルダにあなたの携帯電話のストレージカードのブラックホールでフル解像度の画像を保存することができます
        （フォルダを簡単に見つけるためにアプリでメニューオプションを使用します）。
        ここでは、重力レンズは可能な限り、正確でしようとします - まだそれはまだカメラが見るものすべてが非常に遠く離れていることを前提として -
        これは必ずしも真である必要はありません - 特にあなたの近くにオブジェクトのため。また、近似は事象の地平線（黒丸に非常に正確で近くありません
        途中で - ）事象の地平線の実際のサイズに対応する - 電話のカメラは、限られた、唯一のいくつかの狭いを持っているので、
        視野 - ので、事象の地平線に近いアーティファクトはここに避けられません。このアプリでブラックホールが常に1メートル（3.28フィート）あなたから離れてであると仮定される - この距離を増加させる効果を持っているだろう
        ブラックホールの質量を減少させることとまったく同じ効果。知られている何かを - ブラックホールが使用されている非回転
        球状​​に対称的オブジェクトのための場の方程式のシュヴァルツシルトソリューション。
        \n は
        電話で報告されているように、あなたのバックカメラの視野、次のとおりです。\n \n個
        水平：XXXXXX 度は、\n します
        縦：YYYYYY 度。
        \n は
        \n は
        （1）画像のためのアンドリュー・ハミルトンのためのクレジットを。
    </string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon2_linkify">シュヴァルツシルトソリューション</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ja_description_phenomenon2_link">https://ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E3%82%B7%E3%83%A5%E3%83%AF%E3%83%AB%E3%83%84%E3%82%B7%E3%83%AB%E3%83%88%E8%A7%A3</string>
    <string name="ja_about_app_description1">
        このアプリをご利用いただきありがとうございます、あなたがそれを好きかどうか、それを評価してください:)
        それは完全に無料で、広告なしです。ストアの有料版は、寄付のためだけです。\n\n
        あなたはさらなる進展、バグ修正、翻訳の改善に私をサポートしたい場合、
        あなたはいつもあなたが好きな金額を寄付することができます）\n\n
        それとも、このアプリのための私の小さなサイトを訪問することができます。\n
        \n
        4.2以上のアンドロイド、+32ビットのサポートが正しくカメラのプレビュー（OpenGLの）上のブラックホールをシミュレートするために、GPUに浮かぶが必要です。
        メモリカードに保存され、最終的な高解像度画像は、マルチスレッド方式でCPUに描画される（数によって
        携帯電話上の物理コア）の。
    </string>

    <string name="ja_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_ja.html</string>
    <string name="ja_ovh_page1_linkify">サイト</string>
    <string name="ja_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="ja_donation_link1_linkify">寄付する</string>

</resources>
