<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">BlackHole Cam</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="phototake_name">Photo</string>


    <string name="en_title_tab0_phenomenon">Description</string>
    <string name="en_title_tab1_phenomenon">Support</string>
    <string name="en_progress_title">Saving image</string>
    <string name="en_progress_msg">Wait while processing</string>
    <string name="en_could_not_save_img1">Image could not be saved</string>
    <string name="en_could_not_open_folder">Cannot open/create the image folder</string>
    <string name="en_saved_img1">Image saved</string>
    <string name="en_saving_img_to_sd">Saving processed image to the card</string>
    <string name="en_choose_mass">Select black hole mass</string>
    <string name="en_mass_unit_suffix">of the Earth mass</string>
    <string name="en_menu_openfolder">Open image folder</string>
    <string name="en_menu_preferences">Description</string>
    <string name="en_menu_aboutapp">Support</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon1">
       This application demonstrates the gravitational effect of an small black hole nearby you.
       It uses a back camera of your mobile phone, to see the environment, and then it deflects the
       light rays according to the black hole gravitational pull. The whole effect is called the
       gravitational lens, and can be understood by looking at the picture(1) below - black hole as an red object in the center:
    </string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon1_linkify">gravitational lens</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon1_link">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gravitational_lens</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon2">
        You can change the black hole mass by touching the screen with two fingers and then pinching or spreading them.
        Or, you can use the bottom-right black button to do the same - as you can see then, the black hole mass is of the
        order of inner planet mass - like mars or almost the earth. By clicking the big camera button in the middle,
        you can save the full-resolution image with the black hole on your phone storage card into the separate MyBlackHoles folder
        (use the menu option in the app to find the folder easier).
        The gravity lens here tries to be as accurate, as possible - yet it still assumes that all that the camera sees is very far away -
        which does not have to be necessarily true - especially for the object close to you. Also, the approximation is not very accurate close to the event horizon (black circle
        in the middle - corresponding to the real size of the event horizon) - because the phone camera has only some narrow, limited
        field of view - so the artifacts close to the event horizon are unavoidable here. Black hole in this app is assumed to be always 1 meter (3.28ft) away from you - the effect of increasing this distance would have
        exactly the same effect as decreasing black hole mass. Non-rotating black hole is being used - something known as the
        Schwarzschild solution of the field equations for spherically-symetrical object.
        \n
        Field of view of your back camera, as reported by the phone:\n\n
        horizontal: XXXXXX degrees\n
        vertical  : YYYYYY degrees.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Credit for the Andrew Hamilton for the picture.
    </string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon2_linkify">Schwarzschild solution</string>
    <string name="en_description_phenomenon2_link">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schwarzschild_metric</string>
    <string name="en_about_app_description1">
        Thank you for using this app, please rate it, whether you like it or not :)
        It is completely free and without advertisements. Paid version on the store is only for donation purposes.\n\n
        If you would like to support me in further progress, bugfixing, translation improvement,
        you can always donate any amount you like :)\n\n
        Or you can visit my small webpage for this app.\n
        \n
        Requires android 4.2 or more, + support for 32-bit floats on GPU to correctly simulate black hole on the camera preview(OpenGL).
        Final, high-resolution image saved on memory card is rendered on CPU in a multi-threaded fashion (depending on the number
        of physical cores on the phone).
    </string>

    <string name="en_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_en.html</string>
    <string name="en_ovh_page1_linkify">webpage</string>
    <string name="en_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="en_donation_link1_linkify">donate</string>



    <string name="pl_title_tab0_phenomenon">Opis</string>
    <string name="pl_title_tab1_phenomenon">Wsparcie</string>
    <string name="pl_progress_title">Zapisywanie obrazu</string>
    <string name="pl_progress_msg">Czekaj, przetwarzam</string>
    <string name="pl_could_not_save_img1">Nie udało się zapisać obrazu</string>
    <string name="pl_saved_img1">Obraz zapisano</string>
    <string name="pl_saving_img_to_sd">Zapisywanie przetworzonego obrazka na kartę</string>
    <string name="pl_could_not_open_folder">Nie mogę otworzyć folderu z obrazkami</string>
    <string name="pl_choose_mass">Wybierz masę czarnej dziury</string>
    <string name="pl_mass_unit_suffix">masy Ziemii</string>
    <string name="pl_menu_openfolder">Otwórz folder obrazków</string>
    <string name="pl_menu_preferences">Opis</string>
    <string name="pl_menu_aboutapp">Wsparcie</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon1">
       Ta aplikacja obrazuje efekt grawitacji czarnej dziury na otoczenie. Używa ona tylnej kamerki telefonu
        do rejestracji obrazu i ugięcia promieni świetlnych zgodnie z masą i odległością czarnej dziury od obserwatora.
        Cały efekt nosi nazwę soczewki grawitacyjnej, i jest zobrazowany na obrazku(1) poniżej - czarna dziura jako czerwony obiek w centrum:

    </string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon1_linkify">soczewki grawitacyjnej</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon1_link">https://pl.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soczewkowanie_grawitacyjne</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon2">
       Możesz zmieniać masę czarnej dziury poprzez gest przybliżenia i oddalenia dwoma palcami na ekranie aplikacji. Albo, ten sam
        efekt, wraz z informacją o masie, możesz uzyskać kilkając ikonę w dolnym prawym rogu. Jak widzisz,
        masa czarnej dziury możliwa do ustawienia jest rzędu wielkości mas takich planet jak Mars czy Ziemia.
        Klikając wielki przycisk kamerki na środku, możesz zapisać obrazek z czarną dziurą w pełnej rozdzielczości na kartę pamięci
        twojego telefonu do osobnego folderu MyBlackHoles (w menu opcji jest pozycja co przeniesie cię do tego folderu automatycznie).
        Efekt soczewki grawitacyjnej tutaj stara się być tak wierny rzeczywistości jak możliwe - ale ciągle poddany jest pewnym założeniom uproszczającym -
        jak to że obraz widziany przez kamerkę jest znacznie dalej od czarnej dziury - co nie musi być prawdą dla przedmiotów obok ciebie (kamerka telefonu nie wie jak daleko są widziane przez nią obiekty).
        Również przybliżenie bardzo blisko horyzontu zdarzeń
        (czarne kółko na środku - odpowiadające rzeczywistemu rozmiarowi kątowemu horyzontu zdarzeń)
        nie jest dobre i generuje pewne nieścisłości - kamerka telefonu ma pewne ograniczenie kątowe pola widzenia i promienie światła przechodzące
        zbyt blisko horyzontu zdarzeń nie mają szansy trafić do obserwatora z obszaru widzenia kamerki, gdyż byłyby uginane zbyt mocno.\n
        Czarna dziura jest umiejscowiona w odległości 1m od kamery - zwiększenie tego dystansu 2x wpłynęłoby na obraz tak samo jak zmniejszenie masy
        czarnej dziury dwukrotnie.
        Przybliżone rozwiązanie Schwarzchilda równań ogólnej teorii względności - statyczna, nierotująca czarna dziura, jest tutaj użyte do symulacji.\n
        Pole widzenia twojej tylnej kamery telefonu, wg. systemu:\n\n
        poziomo: XXXXXX stopni\n
        pionowo  : YYYYYY stopni.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Podziękowania za obrazek dla: Andrew Hamilton.
    </string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon2_linkify">rozwiązanie Schwarzchilda</string>
    <string name="pl_description_phenomenon2_link">https://pl.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metryka_Schwarzschilda</string>
    <string name="pl_about_app_description1">
        Dziękuję za skorzystanie z tej applikacji. Jest ona całkowicie darmowa i bez reklam - płatna
        jej wersja na Google Play store
        ma identyczną funkcjonalność i jest jedynie sposobem na wsparcie finansowe.\n\n
        Jeśli chciałbyś mnie wspomóc w dalszym rozwijaniu tej aplikacji, usuwaniu błędów,
        poprawy tłumaczenia, możesz zawsze udzielić wsparcia finansowego :) \n\n
        Możesz również odwiedzić moją małą stronę dla tej aplikacji.\n
        \n
        Wymaga androida 4.2 lub więcej, + wsparcie dla 32-bitowych liczb zmiennoprzecinkowych na GPU do prawidłowego symulowania podglądu(OpenGL). Finalny obraz
        o wysokiej rozdzielczości jest renderowany wielowątkowo na CPU (zależnie od ilości fizycznych rdzeni w telefonie).
    </string>
    <string name="pl_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_pl.html</string>
    <string name="pl_ovh_page1_linkify">stronę</string>
    <string name="pl_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="pl_donation_link1_linkify">wsparcia finansowego</string>















    <string name="zh_title_tab0_phenomenon">描述</string>
    <string name="zh_title_tab1_phenomenon">支持</string>
    <string name="zh_progress_title">保存图像</string>
    <string name="zh_progress_msg">等待处理</string>
    <string name="zh_could_not_save_img1">图像无法保存</string>
    <string name="zh_could_not_open_folder">无法打开/创建图像文件夹</string>
    <string name="zh_saved_img1">图像保存</string>
    <string name="zh_saving_img_to_sd">保存处理后的图像到存储卡</string>
    <string name="zh_choose_mass">选择黑洞质量</string>
    <string name="zh_mass_unit_suffix">地球质量</string>
    <string name="zh_menu_openfolder">打开图像文件夹</string>
    <string name="zh_menu_preferences">描述</string>
    <string name="zh_menu_aboutapp">支持</string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon1">
该应用程序演示附近你一个小的黑洞的引力效应。它使用移动电话的后照相机，看环境，然后将其偏转 根据黑洞引力的光线。整个效果被称为 引力透镜，并且可以通过查看下面的图片（1）可以理解 - 黑洞作为中心的红色物体：
    </string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon1_linkify">引力透镜</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="zh_description_phenomenon1_link">https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%BC%95%E5%8A%9B%E9%80%8F%E9%95%9C</string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon2">你可以用两个手指触摸屏幕，然后挤压或传播这些改变黑洞质量。 或者，你可以使用右下角黑色按钮做同样的 - 你可以看到那么，黑洞质量的 内行星质量的秩序 - 像火星或接近地球。点击中间的大拍照键， 你可以用你的手机存储卡上的黑洞保存全分辨率图像分割成单独的文件夹 MyBlackHoles （使用菜单选项中的应用程序，找到文件夹更容易）。 这里的重力透镜努力做到准确，尽可能 - 但它仍然假定所有的摄像头看到很远的地方 - 这并不必须是一定真 - 特别是对靠近你的对象。此外，近似不是很准确接近事件视界（黑圈 在中间 - 对应于视界的实际大小） - 因为手机照相机仅具有一些窄，有限 视野 - 如此接近的事件视界的文物是不可避免的在这里。在此应用程序黑洞被认为是始终为1米（3.28英尺）离你而去 - 增加这个距离才能产生的效果 正是因为减小黑洞质量相同的效果。非旋转的黑洞正在使用 - 这被称为 为球状对称物体的场方程的史瓦西解。
        \n 看你的背部摄像头领域，所报告的电话：\n\n
        水平：XXXXXX 度的\n
        垂直：YYYYYY 度
        \n
        \n
        （1）信用为安德鲁·汉密尔顿的图片。
    </string>
    <string name="zh_description_phenomenon2_linkify">史瓦西解</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="zh_description_phenomenon2_link">https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%8F%B2%E7%93%A6%E8%A5%BF%E5%BA%A6%E8%A6%8F</string>
    <string name="zh_about_app_description1">
      感谢您使用这个程序，请评价它，不管你喜欢还是不喜欢 :)
        它是完全地免费，无广告。在商店付费版本仅用于捐赠目的。\n\n
        如果你想支持我的进一步进展，错误修复，提高翻译，
        你总是可以捐赠，你喜欢的任何金额 :)\n\n
        或者您也可以访问我为这个应用程序的小网页。\n
        \n
        需要Android4.2以上，+32位支持GPU上的浮正确模拟相机预览（OpenGL的）黑洞。
        保存在存储卡最后，高分辨率图像以多线程方式CPU上呈现（根据数
        在手机上物理核心）。
     </string>

    <string name="zh_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_zh.html</string>
    <string name="zh_ovh_page1_linkify">网页</string>
    <string name="zh_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="zh_donation_link1_linkify">捐赠</string>













    <string name="ja_title_tab0_phenomenon">説明</string>
    <string name="ja_title_tab1_phenomenon">サポート</string>
    <string name="ja_progress_title">画像保存</string>
    <string name="ja_progress_msg">処理中に待ち</string>
    <string name="ja_could_not_save_img1">画像は保存できませんでした</string>
    <string name="ja_could_not_open_folder">開いていない/画像フォルダを作成することができます</string>
    <string name="ja_saved_img1">画像保存</string>
    <string name="ja_saving_img_to_sd">カードに処理された画像を保存します</string>
    <string name="ja_choose_mass">ブラックホールの質量を選択</string>
    <string name="ja_mass_unit_suffix">地球の質量の</string>
    <string name="ja_menu_openfolder">オープン画像フォルダ</string>
    <string name="ja_menu_preferences">説明</string>
    <string name="ja_menu_aboutapp">サポート</string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon1">
        このアプリケーションは、あなたの近くの小さなブラックホールの重力の影響を示しています。
        これは、環境を確認するために、携帯電話のバックカメラを使用し、それは偏向します
        ブラックホール重力に従って光線。全体の効果が呼び出されます
        重力レンズは、以下の画像（1）を見ることによって理解することができる - 中央に赤いオブジェクトとしてブラックホール：
    </string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon1_linkify">重力レンズ</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ja_description_phenomenon1_link">https://ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E9%87%8D%E5%8A%9B%E3%83%AC%E3%83%B3%E3%82%BA</string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon2">
        あなたは、2本の指で画面をタッチし、それらをつまんまたは拡散によってブラックホールの質量を変更することができます。
        それとも、あなたが同じことを行うには、右下の黒いボタンを使用することができます - あなたが見ることができるように、ブラックホールの質量があります
        内側の惑星の質量の順 - 火星またはほぼ地球のような。中央に大きなカメラボタンをクリックすることにより、
        あなたは独立したMyBlackHolesフォルダにあなたの携帯電話のストレージカードのブラックホールでフル解像度の画像を保存することができます
        （フォルダを簡単に見つけるためにアプリでメニューオプションを使用します）。
        ここでは、重力レンズは可能な限り、正確でしようとします - まだそれはまだカメラが見るものすべてが非常に遠く離れていることを前提として -
        これは必ずしも真である必要はありません - 特にあなたの近くにオブジェクトのため。また、近似は事象の地平線（黒丸に非常に正確で近くありません
        途中で - ）事象の地平線の実際のサイズに対応する - 電話のカメラは、限られた、唯一のいくつかの狭いを持っているので、
        視野 - ので、事象の地平線に近いアーティファクトはここに避けられません。このアプリでブラックホールが常に1メートル（3.28フィート）あなたから離れてであると仮定される - この距離を増加させる効果を持っているだろう
        ブラックホールの質量を減少させることとまったく同じ効果。知られている何かを - ブラックホールが使用されている非回転
        球状​​に対称的オブジェクトのための場の方程式のシュヴァルツシルトソリューション。
        \n は
        電話で報告されているように、あなたのバックカメラの視野、次のとおりです。\n \n個
        水平：XXXXXX 度は、\n します
        縦：YYYYYY 度。
        \n
        \n
        （1）画像のためのアンドリュー・ハミルトンのためのクレジットを。
    </string>
    <string name="ja_description_phenomenon2_linkify">シュヴァルツシルトソリューション</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ja_description_phenomenon2_link">https://ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E3%82%B7%E3%83%A5%E3%83%AF%E3%83%AB%E3%83%84%E3%82%B7%E3%83%AB%E3%83%88%E8%A7%A3</string>
    <string name="ja_about_app_description1">
        このアプリをご利用いただきありがとうございます、あなたがそれを好きかどうか、それを評価してください :)
        それは完全に無料で、広告なしです。ストアの有料版は、寄付のためだけです。\n\n
        あなたはさらなる進展、バグ修正、翻訳の改善に私をサポートしたい場合、
        あなたはいつもあなたが好きな金額を寄付することができます）\n\n
        それとも、このアプリのための私の小さなサイトを訪問することができます。\n
        \n
        4.2以上のアンドロイド、+32ビットのサポートが正しくカメラのプレビュー（OpenGLの）上のブラックホールをシミュレートするために、GPUに浮かぶが必要です。メモリカードに保存され、最終的な高解像度画像は、マルチスレッド方式でCPUに描画される（数によって
        携帯電話上の物理コア）の。
    </string>

    <string name="ja_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_ja.html</string>
    <string name="ja_ovh_page1_linkify">サイト</string>
    <string name="ja_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="ja_donation_link1_linkify">寄付する</string>











    <string name="es_title_tab0_phenomenon">Descripción</string>
    <string name="es_title_tab1_phenomenon">Apoyo</string>
    <string name="es_progress_title">imagen Ahorro</string>
    <string name="es_progress_msg">Espere mientras se procesa</string>
    <string name="es_could_not_save_img1">La imagen no pudo ser salvado</string>
    <string name="es_could_not_open_folder">No se puede abrir / crear la carpeta de imágenes</string>
    <string name="es_saved_img1">imagen guardada</string>
    <string name="es_saving_img_to_sd">Guardar la imagen procesada a la tarjeta</string>
    <string name="es_choose_mass">Seleccione la masa del agujero negro</string>
    <string name="es_mass_unit_suffix">de la masa de la Tierra</string>
    <string name="es_menu_openfolder">Abrir carpeta de imágenes</string>
    <string name="es_menu_preferences">Descripción</string>
    <string name="es_menu_aboutapp">Apoyo</string>
    <string name="es_description_phenomenon1">
        Esta aplicación demuestra el efecto gravitacional de un pequeño agujero negro cerca de usted.
        Utiliza una cámara posterior de su teléfono móvil, para ver el medio ambiente, y luego se desvía el los rayos de luz de acuerdo con el agujero negro atracción gravitatoria. El efecto total se denomina lente gravitacional, y puede ser entendido por mirar el cuadro (1) más abajo - agujero negro como un objeto de color rojo en el centro:
    </string>
    <string name="es_description_phenomenon1_linkify">lente gravitacional</string>
    <string name="es_description_phenomenon1_link">https://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lente_gravitacional</string>
    <string name="es_description_phenomenon2">
        Se puede cambiar la masa del agujero negro tocando la pantalla con dos dedos y luego pinchar o propagarlos.
        O bien, puede utilizar el botón negro de abajo a la derecha para hacer lo mismo - como se puede ver a continuación, la masa del agujero negro es de la
        orden de la masa planeta interior - como Marte o casi la tierra. Al hacer clic en el botón de cámara grande en el medio,
        puede guardar la imagen a resolución completa con el agujero negro en su tarjeta de almacenamiento del teléfono en la carpeta separada MyBlackHoles (Utilice la opción de menú en la aplicación para encontrar la carpeta más fácil).
        La lente de la gravedad aquí intenta ser lo más preciso, como sea posible - sin embargo, todavía se supone que todo lo que ve la cámara está muy lejos -
        que no tiene por qué ser necesariamente cierto - especialmente para el objeto cerca de usted. Además, la aproximación no es muy preciso cerca del horizonte de sucesos (círculo negro en el medio - que corresponde al tamaño real del horizonte de sucesos) - debido a que la cámara del teléfono tiene sólo algunos estrecha, limitada
        campo de visión - por lo que los artefactos cerca del horizonte de sucesos son inevitables aquí. agujero negro en esta aplicación se supone que es siempre 1 metro (3.28 pies) de distancia de usted - el efecto de aumentar esta distancia tendría
        exactamente el mismo efecto que la disminución de la masa del agujero negro. No giratoria agujero negro está siendo utilizado - algo que se conoce como el
        solución de Schwarzschild de las ecuaciones de campo de objeto esféricamente simétrica. \n
        Campo de visión de la cámara de nuevo, según lo informado por el teléfono: \n \n
        horizontal: XXXXXX grados \n
        vertical: YYYYYY grados
        \n
        \n
        (1) crédito para el Andrew Hamilton para la foto.
    </string>
    <string name="es_description_phenomenon2_linkify">solución de Schwarzschild</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="es_description_phenomenon2_link">https://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/M%C3%A9trica_de_Schwarzschild</string>
    <string name="es_about_app_description1">
        Gracias por usar esta aplicación, por favor puntúalo, nos guste o no :)
        Es totalmente gratis y sin anuncios. Versión de pago en la tienda es sólo para fines de donación. \n \n
        Si usted quisiera que me apoyen en mayor progreso, fijación de error, mejora de la traducción,
        siempre se puede donar cualquier cantidad que usted tiene gusto :) \n \n
        O puede visitar mi pequeña página web para esta aplicación. \n
        \n
        Requiere Android 4.2 o más, + soporte para 32 bits flota en la GPU para simular correctamente agujero negro en la previa de la cámara (OpenGL).
        Final de alta resolución de imagen, guardada en la tarjeta de memoria en la CPU se representa de un modo multi-hilo (en función del número
        de núcleos físicos en el teléfono).
    </string>

    <string name="es_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_es.html</string>
    <string name="es_ovh_page1_linkify">página web</string>
    <string name="es_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="es_donation_link1_linkify">donar</string>











    <string name="ru_title_tab0_phenomenon">Описание</string>
    <string name="ru_title_tab1_phenomenon">Поддержка</string>
    <string name="ru_progress_title">Сохранение изображений</string>
    <string name="ru_progress_msg">Подождите, пока обработка</string>
    <string name="ru_could_not_save_img1">Изображение не может быть сохранено</string>
    <string name="ru_could_not_open_folder">Не удалось открыть / создать папку с изображениями</string>
    <string name="ru_saved_img1">изображение сохраняется</string>
    <string name="ru_saving_img_to_sd">Сохранение обработанного изображения на карту</string>
    <string name="ru_choose_mass">Выберите массу черной дыры</string>
    <string name="ru_mass_unit_suffix">массы Земли</string>
    <string name="ru_menu_openfolder">Открыть папку изображения</string>
    <string name="ru_menu_preferences">Описание</string>
    <string name="ru_menu_aboutapp">Поддержка</string>
    <string name="ru_description_phenomenon1">
        Это приложение демонстрирует гравитационный эффект с небольшой черной дыры рядом вы.
        Он использует заднюю камеру своего мобильного телефона, чтобы увидеть окружающую среду, а затем он отклоняет
        световые лучи в соответствии с черной дырой тянуть. Весь эффект называется
        гравитационная линза, и можно понять, глядя на картину (1) ниже - черной дыры как красный объект в центре:
    </string>
    <string name="ru_description_phenomenon1_linkify">гравитационная линза</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ru_description_phenomenon1_link">https://ru.wikipedia.org/wiki/%D0%93%D1%80%D0%B0%D0%B2%D0%B8%D1%82%D0%B0%D1%86%D0%B8%D0%BE%D0%BD%D0%BD%D0%B0%D1%8F_%D0%BB%D0%B8%D0%BD%D0%B7%D0%B0</string>
    <string name="ru_description_phenomenon2">
        Вы можете изменить массу черной дыры, касаясь экрана двумя пальцами, а затем щипать или раздвигая их. Или, вы можете использовать кнопку правый нижний черный, чтобы сделать то же самое - как вы можете видеть то, масса черной дыры имеет
        порядок внутренней массы планеты - как Марс или почти на земле. При нажатии на кнопку большой камеры в середине,
        вы можете сохранить в полном разрешении изображение с черной дыры на телефонной карте памяти в отдельную папку MyBlackHoles (Используйте пункт меню в приложение, чтобы найти папку проще).
        Серьезность линза здесь пытается быть настолько точным, насколько это возможно - но все еще предполагает, что все, что видит камера очень далеко -
        который не должен быть обязательно верно - особенно для объекта рядом с вами. Кроме того, приближение не очень точно близко к горизонту событий (черный круг
        в середине - что соответствует реальному размеру горизонта событий) - потому что телефон камера имеет только некоторые узкие, ограниченные
        поле зрения - так артефакты вблизи горизонта событий неизбежны здесь. Черная дыра в этом приложении предполагается всегда 1 метр (3,28 фута) от вас - эффект увеличения этого расстояния будет иметь
        точно такой же эффект, уменьшая массу черной дыры. Невращающийся черная дыра используется - нечто, известное как
        Шварцшильда решение уравнений поля для сферически-симметричной объекта.
        \n
        Поле зрения вашей задней камеры, как сообщил по телефону: \n\n
        горизонтальная: XXXXXX градусов \n
        по вертикали: YYYYYY градусов.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Кредит на Эндрю Гамильтон на картинке.
    </string>
    <string name="ru_description_phenomenon2_linkify">Шварцшильда решение</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ru_description_phenomenon2_link">https://ru.wikipedia.org/wiki/%D0%9C%D0%B5%D1%82%D1%80%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%B0_%D0%A8%D0%B2%D0%B0%D1%80%D1%86%D1%88%D0%B8%D0%BB%D1%8C%D0%B4%D0%B0</string>
    <string name="ru_about_app_description1">
        Благодарим Вас за использование этого приложения, пожалуйста, оцените его, нравится ли вам это или нет :)
        Это абсолютно бесплатно и без рекламы. Платная версия на магазине только для целей донорства. \n \n
        Если вы хотели бы поддержать меня в дальнейшем прогрессе, исправление ошибок, улучшение перевода,
        вы всегда можете пожертвовать любую сумму, которую вы любите:) \n \n
        Или же вы можете посетить мой небольшой веб-страницу для этого приложения. \n
        \n
        Требуется Android версии 4.2 или более, + поддержка 32-битных плавает на GPU, чтобы правильно смоделировать черную дыру на камеры предварительного просмотра (OpenGL).
        Заключительный, с высоким разрешением изображения, сохраненные на карте памяти оказывается на CPU в многопоточном моды (в зависимости от количества
        физических ядер на телефоне).
    </string>

    <string name="ru_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_ru.html</string>
    <string name="ru_ovh_page1_linkify">веб-страницу</string>
    <string name="ru_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="ru_donation_link1_linkify">жертвовать</string>





    <string name="de_title_tab0_phenomenon">Beschreibung</string>
    <string name="de_title_tab1_phenomenon">Unterstützen</string>
    <string name="de_progress_title">Speichern von Bild</string>
    <string name="de_progress_msg">Warten Sie, während der Verarbeitung</string>
    <string name="de_could_not_save_img1">Bild konnte nicht gespeichert werden</string>
    <string name="de_could_not_open_folder">Kann nicht öffnen / erstellen Sie den Bildordner</string>
    <string name="de_saved_img1">Bild gespeichert</string>
    <string name="de_saving_img_to_sd">Speichern von verarbeiteten Bilds auf der Karte</string>
    <string name="de_choose_mass">Wählen Masse des Schwarzen Lochs</string>
    <string name="de_mass_unit_suffix">der Erdmasse</string>
    <string name="de_menu_openfolder">Bild öffnen Ordner</string>
    <string name="de_menu_preferences">Beschreibung</string>
    <string name="de_menu_aboutapp">Unterstützen</string>
    <string name="de_description_phenomenon1">
        Diese Anwendung zeigt die Gravitationswirkung eines kleinen schwarzen Loch in der Nähe Sie.
        Es verwendet eine rückseitige Kamera Ihres Mobiltelefons , um die Umwelt zu sehen, und dann lenkt es das
        Lichtstrahlen nach dem schwarzen Loch Anziehungskraft . Der gesamte Effekt wird genannt
        Gravitationslinse und kann durch einen Blick auf das Bild (1) unten verstanden werden - schwarzes Loch als ein rotes Objekt in der Mitte:
    </string>
    <string name="de_description_phenomenon1_linkify">Gravitationslinse</string>
    <string name="de_description_phenomenon1_link">https://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gravitationslinseneffekt</string>
    <string name="de_description_phenomenon2">
        Sie können die Masse des Schwarzen Lochs ändern, indem Sie den Bildschirm mit zwei Fingern zu berühren und dann kneifen oder sie zu verbreiten.
        Alternativ können Sie auch die rechte untere schwarze Taste verwenden, das gleiche zu tun - wie man dann sehen kann, ist die Masse des Schwarzen Lochs ist von der
        Reihenfolge der inneren Planetenmasse - wie Mars oder fast die Erde. Durch die große Kamera-Taste in der Mitte klicken,
        können Sie die Vollauflösendes Bild mit dem schwarzen Loch auf Ihrem Telefon die Speicherkarte in den separaten MyBlackHoles Ordner speichern
        (Verwenden Sie die Menüoption in der App die Ordner leichter zu finden).
        Die Schwere Linse hier versucht, so genau, wie möglich zu sein - doch es geht weiterhin davon aus, dass alles, was die Kamera sieht, ist sehr weit weg -
        das muss nicht unbedingt der Fall sein - vor allem für das Objekt Ihrer Nähe. Auch ist die Näherung nicht sehr genau der Nähe des Ereignishorizonts (schwarzer Kreis
        in der Mitte - entsprechend der tatsächlichen Größe des Ereignishorizont) - weil die Handy-Kamera nur einige schmale hat, begrenzt
        Sichtfeld - so die Artefakte der Nähe des Ereignishorizonts sind hier unumgänglich. Schwarzes Loch in dieser App wird davon ausgegangen, von Ihnen immer 1 Meter (3.28ft) weg zu sein - um die Wirkung dieser Strecke zu erhöhen würde
        genau die gleiche Wirkung wie Masse des Schwarzen Lochs abnimmt. Nicht rotierende Schwarze Loch verwendet wird - etwas, bekannt als die
        Schwarzschild-Lösung der Feldgleichungen für sphärisch symetrical Objekt.
        \n
        Sichtfeld der Kamera zurück, wie das Telefon gemeldet: \n \n
        horizontal: XXXXXX Grad \n
        vertikal: YYYYYY Grad.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Kredit für die Andrew Hamilton für das Bild.
    </string>
    <string name="de_description_phenomenon2_linkify">Schwarzschild-Lösung</string>
    <string name="de_description_phenomenon2_link">https://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schwarzschild-Metrik</string>
    <string name="de_about_app_description1">
        Vielen Dank für die Nutzung dieser App, bewerten Sie es, ob Sie es mögen oder nicht :) Es ist völlig kostenlos und ohne Werbung. Paid-Version auf dem Speicher ist nur für die Spende Zwecke. \n \n
        Wenn Sie möchten, dass ich in weitere Fortschritte zu unterstützen, Fehler Fixierung, Übersetzung Verbesserung,
        Sie können immer jede Menge spenden Sie:) \n \n
        Oder Sie können meine kleine Webseite für diese App zu besuchen. \n
        \n
        Erfordert Android 4.2 oder mehr beträgt, + Unterstützung für 32-Bit auf GPU auf der Kameravorschau (OpenGL) richtig zu simulieren schwarzes Loch schwimmt.
        Finale, hochauflösendes Bild auf der Speicherkarte gespeichert auf CPU in einem Multi-Threaded Mode gemacht wird (abhängig von der Anzahl
        von physischen Kerne am Telefon).
    </string>

    <string name="de_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_de.html</string>
    <string name="de_ovh_page1_linkify">Webseite</string>
    <string name="de_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="de_donation_link1_linkify">spenden</string>






    <string name="fr_title_tab0_phenomenon">La description</string>
    <string name="fr_title_tab1_phenomenon">Soutien</string>
    <string name="fr_progress_title">l\'image enregistrement</string>
    <string name="fr_progress_msg">Attendez que le traitement</string>
    <string name="fr_could_not_save_img1">Image n\'a pas pu être sauvé</string>
    <string name="fr_could_not_open_folder">Vous ne pouvez pas ouvrir / créer le dossier d\'image</string>
    <string name="fr_saved_img1">image enregistrée</string>
    <string name="fr_saving_img_to_sd">Enregistrement image traitée à la carte</string>
    <string name="fr_choose_mass">Sélectionnez la masse du trou noir</string>
    <string name="fr_mass_unit_suffix">de la masse de la Terre</string>
    <string name="fr_menu_openfolder">dossier d\'images Ouvrir</string>
    <string name="fr_menu_preferences">La description</string>
    <string name="fr_menu_aboutapp">Soutien</string>
    <string name="fr_description_phenomenon1">
        Cette application démontre l\'effet gravitationnel d\'un petit trou noir à proximité vous.
        Il utilise une caméra arrière de votre téléphone mobile, pour voir l\'environnement, et il dévie le rayons lumineux selon le trou noir attraction gravitationnelle. L\'effet entier est appelé
        lentille gravitationnelle, et peut être compris en regardant l\'image (1) ci-dessous - trou noir comme un objet rouge au centre:
    </string>
    <string name="fr_description_phenomenon1_linkify">lentille gravitationnelle</string>
    <string name="fr_description_phenomenon1_link">https://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lentille_gravitationnelle</string>
    <string name="fr_description_phenomenon2">
        Vous pouvez changer la masse du trou noir en touchant l\'écran avec deux doigts, puis pincer ou de les propager.
        Ou, vous pouvez utiliser le bouton noir en bas à droite pour faire la même chose - comme vous pouvez le voir ensuite, la masse du trou noir est de la
        ordre de masse planète intérieure - comme mars ou presque la terre. En cliquant sur le gros bouton de la caméra dans le milieu,
        vous pouvez enregistrer l\'image en pleine résolution avec le trou noir sur votre téléphone carte de stockage dans le dossier MyBlackHoles séparé
        (Utilisez l\'option de menu dans l\'application pour trouver le dossier plus facile).
        La lentille de gravité ici tente d\'être aussi précis, que possible - mais il suppose encore que tout ce que voit la caméra est très loin -
        qui ne doit pas être nécessairement vrai - en particulier pour l\'objet près de chez vous. En outre, le rapprochement est pas très précis à proximité de l\'horizon des événements (cercle noir
        au milieu - correspondant à la taille réelle de l\'horizon des événements) - parce que la caméra de téléphone ne dispose que d\'une partie étroite, limitée
        champ de vision - de sorte que les objets proches de l\'horizon des événements sont inévitables ici. Trou noir dans cette application est supposé être toujours 1 mètre (3.28ft) loin de vous - l\'effet d\'augmenter cette distance aurait
        exactement le même effet que la diminution de la masse du trou noir. Non-trou noir en rotation est utilisée - quelque chose de connu sous le nom
        solution de Schwarzschild des équations de champ pour l\'objet sphériquement symétrique.
        \n
        Champ de vision de votre appareil photo, tel que rapporté par le téléphone: \n \n
        horizontal: XXXXXX degrés \n
        degrés de YYYYYY: vertical.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Crédit pour Andrew Hamilton pour la photo.
    </string>
    <string name="fr_description_phenomenon2_linkify">solution de Schwarzschild</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="fr_description_phenomenon2_link">https://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/M%C3%A9trique_de_Schwarzschild</string>
    <string name="fr_about_app_description1"> Merci d\'utiliser cette application, s\'il vous plaît noter, que ça vous plaise ou non :)
        Il est entièrement gratuit et sans publicité. Version payante sur le magasin est uniquement à des fins de dons. \n \n
        Si vous souhaitez me soutenir dans de nouveaux progrès, fixation d\'erreur, l\'amélioration de la traduction,
        vous pouvez toujours faire un don de tout montant que vous voulez:) \n \n
        Ou vous pouvez visiter ma petite page Web pour cette application. \n
        \n
        Nécessite Android 4.2 ou plus, + support pour 32 bits flotte sur GPU pour simuler correctement le trou noir sur la prévisualisation de la caméra (OpenGL).
        Final, image haute résolution enregistrée sur la carte mémoire est rendu sur le processeur dans un mode multi-thread (en fonction du nombre
        de cœurs physiques sur le téléphone).
    </string>

    <string name="fr_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_fr.html</string>
    <string name="fr_ovh_page1_linkify">page Web</string>
    <string name="fr_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="fr_donation_link1_linkify">faire un don</string>





    <string name="it_title_tab0_phenomenon">Descrizione</string>
    <string name="it_title_tab1_phenomenon">Supporto</string>
    <string name="it_progress_title">Salvataggio di immagini</string>
    <string name="it_progress_msg">Attendere durante l\'elaborazione</string>
    <string name="it_could_not_save_img1">Immagine non poteva essere salvato</string>
    <string name="it_could_not_open_folder">Non può aprire / creare la cartella dell\'immagine</string>
    <string name="it_saved_img1">immagine salvata</string>
    <string name="it_saving_img_to_sd">Salvataggio immagine elaborata sulla scheda</string>
    <string name="it_choose_mass">Selezionare massa del buco nero</string>
    <string name="it_mass_unit_suffix">della massa terrestre</string>
    <string name="it_menu_openfolder">Apri cartella di immagini</string>
    <string name="it_menu_preferences">Descrizione</string>
    <string name="it_menu_aboutapp">Supporto</string>
    <string name="it_description_phenomenon1">
        Questa applicazione dimostra l\'effetto gravitazionale di un piccolo buco nero nelle vicinanze si.
        Esso utilizza una fotocamera posteriore del telefono cellulare, per vedere l\'ambiente, e poi si devia il
        raggi di luce in base alla forza gravitazionale buco nero. L\'effetto complessivo è chiamato
        lente gravitazionale, e può essere compreso da guardando la foto (1) di seguito - buco nero come un oggetto rosso al centro:
    </string>
    <string name="it_description_phenomenon1_linkify">lente gravitazionale</string>
    <string name="it_description_phenomenon1_link">https://it.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lente_gravitazionale</string>
    <string name="it_description_phenomenon2">
        È possibile modificare la massa del buco nero toccando lo schermo con due dita e poi pizzicare o diffusione.
        In alternativa, è possibile utilizzare il pulsante nero in basso a destra a fare lo stesso - come si può vedere, allora, la massa del buco nero è del ordine della massa pianeta interno - come Marte o quasi la terra. Cliccando sul pulsante grande macchina fotografica nel mezzo,
        è possibile salvare l\'immagine a piena risoluzione con il buco nero sulla scheda di memoria del telefono nella cartella separata MyBlackHoles
        (Utilizzare l\'opzione di menu in app per trovare la cartella più facile).
        La lente gravitazionale qui cerca di essere il più precisi, per quanto possibile - ma assume ancora che tutto ciò che la fotocamera vede è molto lontano -
        che non deve essere necessariamente vero - soprattutto per l\'oggetto vicino a voi. Inoltre, l\'approssimazione non è molto preciso vicino all\'orizzonte degli eventi (cerchio nero
        nel mezzo - corrispondente alla dimensione reale della orizzonte degli eventi) - in quanto la fotocamera del telefono ha solo un po \'stretta, limitata
        campo di vista - così i manufatti vicino all\'orizzonte degli eventi sono inevitabili qui. Buco nero in questa applicazione si presume che sia sempre 1 metro (3.28Ft) lontano da voi - l\'effetto di aumentare questa distanza avrebbe
        esattamente lo stesso effetto di diminuire la massa buco nero. Non rotante buco nero è in uso - qualcosa conosciuto come il
        soluzione di Schwarzschild delle equazioni di campo per oggetto sferico-simmetrico.
        \n
        Il campo di vista della fotocamera posteriore, come riportato dal telefono: \n \n
        orizzontale: XXXXXX gradi \n
        YYYYYY: verticale.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Credito per l\'Andrew Hamilton per l\'immagine.
    </string>
    <string name="it_description_phenomenon2_linkify">soluzione di Schwarzschild</string>
    <string name="it_description_phenomenon2_link">https://it.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spazio-tempo_di_Schwarzschild</string>
    <string name="it_about_app_description1">
        Grazie per aver usato questa applicazione, si prega di votarla, che vi piaccia o no :)
        E \'completamente gratuito e senza pubblicità. versione a pagamento sul negozio è solo a scopo di donazione. \n \n
        Se volete sostenermi in ulteriore progresso, fissaggio errore, miglioramento traduzione,
        si può sempre donare qualsiasi importo che gradite :) \n \n
        Oppure si può visitare il mio piccolo sito per questa applicazione. \n
        Finale ad alta risoluzione, salvati su scheda di memoria viene resa su CPU in modo multi-threaded (a seconda del numero di core fisici al telefono).
    </string>

    <string name="it_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_it.html</string>
    <string name="it_ovh_page1_linkify">piccolo sito</string>
    <string name="it_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="it_donation_link1_linkify">donare</string>







    <string name="ar_title_tab0_phenomenon"> وصف </string>
    <string name="ar_title_tab1_phenomenon"> الدعم </string>
    <string name="ar_progress_title"> صورة إنقاذ </string>
    <string name="ar_progress_msg"> الانتظار لحين تجهيز </string>
    <string name="ar_could_not_save_img1"> لا يمكن حفظ صورة </string>
    <string name="ar_could_not_open_folder"> لا يمكن فتح / إنشاء مجلد الصور </string>
    <string name="ar_saved_img1"> الصورة المحفوظة </string>
    <string name="ar_saving_img_to_sd"> إنقاذ صورة المصنعة لبطاقة </string>
    <string name="ar_choose_mass"> تحديد كتلة الثقب الأسود </string>
    <string name="ar_mass_unit_suffix"> من كتلة الأرض </string>
    <string name="ar_menu_openfolder"> مجلد الصور المفتوح </string>
    <string name="ar_menu_preferences"> وصف </string>
    <string name="ar_menu_aboutapp"> الدعم </string>
    <string name="ar_description_phenomenon1">
يوضح هذا التطبيق من تأثير جاذبية الثقب الأسود صغير قريب لك.
        ويستخدم الكاميرا الخلفية للهاتف المحمول، لمعرفة البيئة، وبعد ذلك ينحرف عن
        الأشعة الضوئية وفقا لثقب أسود الجاذبية. ويطلق على تأثير كله
        عدسة الجاذبية، ويمكن فهمها من خلال النظر في الصورة (1) أدناه - الثقب الأسود ككائن الأحمر في المركز:
    </string>
    <string name="ar_description_phenomenon1_linkify"> عدسة الجاذبية </string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ar_description_phenomenon1_link"> https://ar.wikipedia.org/wiki/%D8%B9%D8%AF%D8%B3%D8%A9_%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AC%D8%A7%D8%B0%D8%A8%D9%8A%D8%A9 </string>
    <string name="ar_description_phenomenon2">

        يمكنك تغيير كتلة الثقب الأسود عن طريق لمس الشاشة مع اثنين من أصابع ثم معسر أو نشرها.
        أو، يمكنك استخدام الزر الأسود الأيمن السفلي لتفعل الشيء نفسه - كما ترون ذلك الحين، وكتلة الثقب الأسود هي من
        ترتيب كتلة الكوكب الداخلية - مثل المريخ أو ما يقرب من الأرض. بالضغط على زر الكاميرا كبير في الوسط،
        يمكنك حفظ الصورة كامل القرار مع الثقب الأسود على بطاقة تخزين الهاتف الخاص بك إلى مجلد منفصل MyBlackHoles
        (استخدام خيار القائمة في تطبيق للعثور على مجلد أسهل).
        تحاول عدسة الجاذبية هنا لتكون دقيقة، وقت ممكن - ومع ذلك لا يزال يفترض أن كل ما تراه الكاميرا هي بعيدة جدا -
        الذي ليس من الضروري أن يكون صحيحا بالضرورة - خاصة بالنسبة للكائن قريب منك. أيضا، وتقريب ليست قريبة دقيقة للغاية إلى أفق الحدث (دائرة سوداء
        في الوسط - الموافق الحجم الحقيقي للأفق الحدث) - لأن الكاميرا الهاتف لديه سوى بعض ضيقة، محدودة
        مجال الرؤية - حتى القطع الأثرية على مقربة من أفق الحدث لا يمكن تجنبها هنا. ومن المفترض الثقب الأسود في هذا التطبيق ليكون دائما 1 متر (3.28ft) بعيدا عنك - تأثير من شأنه زيادة هذه المسافة ديك
        بالضبط نفس تأثير انخفاض كتلة الثقب الأسود. يتم استخدامه غير الدورية الثقب الأسود - ما يعرف باسم
        حل شوارزشيلد من معادلات المجال لكائن كرويا متناظرة.
        
        مجال الرؤية من الكاميرا الخلفية الخاصة بك، كما ذكرت عن طريق الهاتف:
        درجة XXXXXX: أفقي
        درجة YYYYYY: الرأسي.
        
        
        (1) الائتمان لأندرو هاملتون للصورة.

    </string>
    <string name="ar_description_phenomenon2_linkify"> حل شوارزشيلد </string>
    <string formatted="false" name="ar_description_phenomenon2_link"> https://ar.wikipedia.org/wiki/%D9%85%D8%B5%D9%81%D9%88%D9%81%D8%A9_%D8%B4%D9%88%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%B2%D8%B4%D9%8A%D9%84%D8%AF </string>
    <string name="ar_about_app_description1">

        شكرا لكم لاستخدام هذا التطبيق، يرجى تقييم ذلك، ما إذا كنت ترغب في ذلك أم لا :)
         فهو حر تماما وبدون إعلانات. النسخة المدفوعة على متجر ليست سوى لأغراض التبرع.
         إذا كنت ترغب في دعم لي في إحراز المزيد من التقدم، وتحديد الخطأ، وتحسين الترجمة،
         يمكنك التبرع دائما أي مبلغ تريده :)
         أو يمكنك زيارة صفحتي الصغيرة لهذا التطبيق.
         
         يتطلب الروبوت 4.2 أو أكثر، + دعم 32 بت يطفو على GPU لمحاكاة الثقب الأسود على معاينة الكاميرا (برنامج OpenGL) بشكل صحيح.
         يتم تقديم النهائية، عالية الدقة صورة محفوظة على بطاقة الذاكرة على وحدة المعالجة المركزية بطريقة متعددة الخيوط (اعتمادا على عدد
         من النوى الفعلية على الهاتف).

    </string>

    <string name="ar_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_ar.html</string>
    <string name="ar_ovh_page1_linkify"> صفحتي </string>
    <string name="ar_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="ar_donation_link1_linkify"> تبرع </string>







    <string name="pt_title_tab0_phenomenon">Descrição</string>
    <string name="pt_title_tab1_phenomenon">Apoio</string>
    <string name="pt_progress_title">Imagem Economia</string>
    <string name="pt_progress_msg">Aguarde enquanto o processamento</string>
    <string name="pt_could_not_save_img1">A imagem não poderia ser salvo</string>
    <string name="pt_could_not_open_folder">Não é possível abrir / criar a pasta de imagem</string>
    <string name="pt_saved_img1">imagem salva</string>
    <string name="pt_saving_img_to_sd">Salvando imagem processada para o cartão</string>
    <string name="pt_choose_mass">Escolha massa do buraco negro</string>
    <string name="pt_mass_unit_suffix">da massa de terra</string>
    <string name="pt_menu_openfolder">Abrir pasta de imagem</string>
    <string name="pt_menu_preferences">Descrição</string>
    <string name="pt_menu_aboutapp">Apoio</string>
    <string name="pt_description_phenomenon1">
        Esta aplicação demonstra o efeito gravitacional de um pequeno buraco negro nas proximidades você.
        Ele usa uma câmera traseira de seu telefone móvel, para ver o ambiente e, em seguida, ele desvia o
        os raios de luz de acordo com a força gravitacional do buraco negro. O efeito é chamado de conjunto
        lente gravitacional, e pode ser compreendida olhando para a foto (1) abaixo - buraco negro como um objeto vermelho no centro:
    </string>
    <string name="pt_description_phenomenon1_linkify">lente gravitacional</string>
    <string name="pt_description_phenomenon1_link">https://pt.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lente_gravitacional</string>
    <string name="pt_description_phenomenon2">
        Você pode alterar a massa do buraco negro tocando a tela com dois dedos e, em seguida, beliscar ou espalhá-los.
        Ou, você pode usar o botão preto inferior direito de fazer o mesmo - como você pode ver, em seguida, a massa do buraco negro é do
        ordem de massa planeta interior - como Marte ou quase a terra. Ao clicar no botão câmera grande no meio,
        você pode salvar a imagem de alta resolução com o buraco negro em seu cartão de memória do telefone para a pasta MyBlackHoles separada
        (Use a opção de menu no aplicativo para encontrar a pasta mais fácil).
        A lente gravidade aqui tenta ser o mais preciso, quanto possível - mas ainda assume que tudo o que a câmera vê é muito longe -
        que não tem que ser necessariamente verdade - especialmente para o objeto perto de você. Além disso, a aproximação não é muito preciso perto do horizonte de eventos (círculo preto
        no meio - correspondente ao tamanho real do horizonte de eventos) - porque a câmera do telefone tem apenas alguns estreita, limitada
        campo de visão - para que os artefatos perto do horizonte de eventos são inevitáveis ​​aqui. buraco negro neste app é assumido como sendo sempre um metro (3,28 pés) longe de você - o efeito de aumentar essa distância teria
        exatamente o mesmo efeito de diminuir a massa do buraco negro. Não rotativa buraco negro está sendo usado - algo conhecido como
        solução de Schwarzschild das equações de campo para o objeto esférico-simétricas.
        \n
        Campo de visão de sua câmera de volta, conforme relatado pelo telefone: \n \n
        horizontal: XXXXXX graus \n
        graus YYYYYY: vertical.
        \n
        \n
        (1) Crédito para o Andrew Hamilton para a imagem.
    </string>
    <string name="pt_description_phenomenon2_linkify">solução de Schwarzschild</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="pt_description_phenomenon2_link">https://pt.wikipedia.org/wiki/M%C3%A9trica_de_Schwarzschild</string>
    <string name="pt_about_app_description1">
        Obrigado por usar este aplicativo, por favor classifique-lo, quer você goste ou não :)
        É totalmente gratuito e sem propagandas. versão paga na loja é apenas para fins de doação. \n \n
        Se você gostaria de me apoiar em maior progresso, correções de bugs, melhorias de tradução,
        você sempre pode doar qualquer quantia que quiser:) \n \n
        Ou você pode visitar a minha pequena página da web para este app. \n
        \n
        Requer Android 4.2 ou mais, + suporte para 32-bit flutua na GPU para simular corretamente buraco negro na visualização da câmera (OpenGL). imagem final, de alta resolução, salvo no cartão de memória é processado na CPU de uma forma multi-threaded (dependendo do número de núcleos físicos no telefone).
    </string>

    <string name="pt_ovh_page1">http://wrobel731.ovh.org/blackholecam/main_pt.html</string>
    <string name="pt_ovh_page1_linkify">página da web</string>
    <string name="pt_donation_link1">https://www.QWEQWL.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;giarws_vyrrib_id=Z2TVKTC6NHQLE</string>
    <string name="pt_donation_link1_linkify">doar</string>



</resources>
